Troy Weaver

Software Developer

Fishers, IN • (317) 332-1231 • troylw@gmail.com • Professional Portfolio

SUMMARY

My background is different than that of most software developers as I had a successful career in real estate and lease management for over a decade before deciding to pursue my passion. I will bring that experience with me, along with unmatched determination to succeed in my new field.

EXPERIENCE

L&W Outdoor Advertising, Inc., Greenfield - Real Estate/Lease Manager

April 2010 - January 2022

- Managed approximately 200 sign leases by maintaining contact with all leaseholders and negotiating lease renewals
- Acquired new sign leases through extensive research on zoning classifications and sign regulations
- Obtained sign permits, land surveys, title policies, and all other documents required for closing real estate transactions

Angie's List (now Angi), Indianapolis - Customer Service Rep

September 2007 - April 2010

- Answered customer emails and phone calls covering a variety of concerns
- Encouraged prospective customers to sign up for the paid service
- Proofread and edited customer reports before they were posted

EDUCATION

Indiana University, Bloomington - Bachelor of Arts Degree

2003 - 2007

Majors in Psychology and Criminal Justice

OTHER QUALIFICATIONS

- Indiana Real Estate Broker License #RB14042601
- CIW Advanced HTML5 and CSS3 Specialist

PROFESSIONAL REFERENCES

Steve Jewell, L&W Outdoor Advertising, Inc. - Sales Representative

(317) 442-7785

Steve and I worked together in a small office setting for the entire 12 years I was at L&W, and he has been involved in the sign industry his entire life. He knows my professional experience better than anyone.

Alisha Blankenship, Witty Dog Designs, LLC - Owner/Graphic Designer

(317) 459-4282

Witty Dog Designs, LLC was a subcontractor for L&W. Alisha designed the majority of our billboard advertisements, and I worked directly with her on creating and maintaining L&W's website.

Randy Worland, MWP Fabrications - Owner/Fabricator

(317) 642-6879

Randy worked at L&W the first 10 years I was with the company before leaving to start his own business. I have known Randy since I first interned with L&W in 2005.